solvemedia.com 2014-11-15

# Solve Media

SOLVE MEDIA, INC. WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

Effective: July 07, 2014

We at Solve Media are committed to respecting your privacy choices. This Website Privacy Policy only applies to the information collected on the publicly-available sections of the website, [www.solvemedia.com](http://www.solvemedia.com/), including any versions optimized for viewing on a wireless or tablet device (the "Website"), however accessed and/or used. We have established this Privacy Policy to tell you about the type of information we may gather during your visit to the Website, how we use and share your information, and how you can manage your information.

This Website Privacy Policy does not apply to:

  * Information that you may submit to us offline or to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we may link or who may link to us. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third party websites. 
  * Solve Media's hosted advertising platform delivered to customers as software-as-a-service ("SaaS"). To understand how Solve Media handles its Customer's personally identifiable information with respect to Solve Media's SaaS, please consult your Publisher Agreement governing that service.
  * Consumer data collected through online CAPTCHAs. For more information about Solve Media's consumer privacy practices and models, including its collection of information through CAPTCHAs and cookies, visit [portal.solvemedia.com/portal/public/privacy](https://portal.solvemedia.com/portal/public/privacy) .

**By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.**

**I. _What Information Is Collected and Stored?_**

We may collect two basic types of information from you in conjunction with your use of the Website: personally identifiable information ("PII") and non-personally identifiable information (non-PII). Personally identifiable information is any information that can individually identify you and includes, among other things, information that you may supply to us when you visit the Website, e.g., your company name, your name, e-mail address, postal address, and telephone number. Non-personally identifiable information includes information that does not identify you personally, but it may include tracking and usage information about your location, demographics, use of the Website and the Internet.

**A. Personally Identifiable Information**

As a general matter, you can browse the Website without submitting your PII to us. However, there are a number of circumstances in which you may supply us with your PII, such as when you request customer service or sales help or when you post comments on our blog.

**B. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information From or Through Social Media Sites**

When you interact with any Solve Media social media platform, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google+, or LinkedIn, we may collect the PII that you make available to us on that page or account including your account ID.

**C. Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

In addition, when you interact with the Website, we may collect certain information that does not identify you individually and our servers may automatically keep an activity log of your use of the Website ("non-personally identifiable information" or "non-PII"), such as device information about your computer, mobile device, or other device that you use to access the Website. This information may include IP address, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language, and other transactional information. We may also collect usage information about your use of the Website, such as a reading history of the pages you view, or additional "traffic data," such as the time and date of access, software crash reports, session identification number and referring website addresses. We use this information to provide you a more customized experience on the Website. 

**D. Collection of Personally and Non-Personally Identifiable Information From Other Sources**

We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources (including by us from our offline interactions with you) to, among other things, enable us to verify, update and correct the information contained in our database and to better customize your experience on the Website.

**E. Cookies and Other Online Tracking Technologies**

Like many websites, we use "cookies", which are small text files that are stored on your computer or equipment when you visit certain online pages that record your preferences and actions. We use cookies to track use of our Website. We may also use cookies to monitor traffic, improve the Website and make it easier and/or relevant for your use.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to disable or reject cookies. If you delete your cookies or if you set your web browser to decline cookies, some features of the Website may not work or may not work as designed. For more information on cookies and how to disable them, check out our Cookie and Tracking FAQs or visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by unaffiliated third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used.

Your browser or device may include "Do Not Track" functionality. Because a "Do Not Track" compliance protocol has not yet been finalized, Solve Media's information collection and disclosure practices, and the choices that we provide to customers, will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received. To learn more about the use of this information or to choose not to have this information used by our third party advertising partners by opting out, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**II. _How Do We Use Your Information?_**

We use the information we learn from you to help us personalize and continually improve your experience on the Website. We may use your personally and non-personally identifiable information to:

  * Provide you with the content you request
  * Communicate with you about changes to our policies and send you information about features and enhancements on or to our Website
  * Send you information about our products and services, third party products and services, or special events by e-mail, text, or other another medium
  * Optimize or improve our products, services and operations
  * Detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal
  * Perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of users of the Websites and their purchasing patterns

We may also use and/or combine information that we collect off-line, or that we collect or receive from third party sources, to enhance, expand, and check the accuracy of user records.

**III. _Who Do We Share Your Information With?_**

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose information about your personally identifiable information collected online to any organizations not part of Solve Media or its subsidiaries or related entities, except as described below. Although we may provide your information to our agents, affiliates, and partners, in no event will we sell or rent your PII as part of a customer list or similar transaction.

**A. Third-Party Agents**

We have third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and partners that perform functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to, marketing, analytics, and customer service. These entities may have access to personally identifiable information if needed to perform their functions. If such access is required, the third parties will be contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that PII. They are restricted from using, selling, distributing or altering this data in any way other than to provide the requested services to the Website.

**B. Business Partners and Other Third Parties**

We may share your personally identifiable information with our business partners or co-marketers from time to time. We may also share your PII with third parties that provide products and services that we think you may be interested in. You may withdraw your consent to our sharing of your PII with business partners and third parties at any time by following the opt-out process described below.

**C. Assignment**

We may change our ownership or corporate organization while providing the Website. We may also sell certain assets associated with the Website. As a result, please be aware that in such event we may transfer some or all of your information to an entity acquiring all or part of our assets or to another company with which we have merged. Under such circumstances we would, to the extent possible, require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. Nevertheless, we cannot promise that an acquiring company or the merged company will have the same privacy practices or treat your information the same as described in this Privacy Policy.

**D. Law Enforcement, Legal Process, and Emergency Situations**

We may use or disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Website; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, the Website or our users, and (c) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Website or the public.

**E. Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We may disclose or share non-personally identifiable information (or other information, other than PII) in any other manner that we deem appropriate or necessary. Among other things, we will disclose non-PII to third parties to help us determine how people use parts of the Website and who our users are so we can improve our Website. We will also disclose non-PII to our partners and other third parties about how our users collectively use the Sites.

**IV. _How Can You Opt-Out?_**

You may opt-out of having your personally identifiable information shared with business partners and third parties by sending an email to [privacy@solvemedia.com](mailto:privacy@solvemedia.com) with "CUSTOMER OPT-OUT" in the subject line.

You may always opt-out of receiving future e-mail marketing messages and non-transactional communications from Solve Media. We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications from us by clicking the "UNSUBSCRIBE" link located at the bottom of any Solve Media marketing email. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with Solve Media.

To request the correction or deletion any personally identifiable information that you have provided to us, send an email to [privacy@solvemedia.com](mailto:privacy@solvemedia.com) with "ACCESS AND CORRECT INFORMATION" in the subject line. You will not be permitted to examine the personally identifiable information of any other person or entity and may be required to provide us with personally identifiable information to verify your identity prior to accessing any records containing information about you. We may not accommodate a request to change or delete personally identifiable information if we believe doing so would violate any law or legal requirement, or cause the information to be incorrect.

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to process all opt-out and access requests in a timely manner.

If you are a consumer who wants to opt-out of Solve-Media's advertising databases, please visit our opt-out page at [portal.solvemedia.com/portal/public/opt-out](https://portal.solvemedia.com/portal/public/opt-out)

**V. _Other Important Information_**

**_How Do We Secure Your Information?_**

We maintain commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure your information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, we are unable to guarantee that security measures we take will not be penetrated or compromised or that your information will remain secure under all circumstances.

**_How Long Do We Keep Personally Identifiable Information?_**

The time period for which we keep information varies according to what the information is used for. In some cases, there are legal requirements to keep data for a minimum period. Unless there is a specific legal requirement for us to keep the information, we will retain it for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the data was collected or for which it is to be further processed.

**_Public and Community Areas_**

Please remember that any information you share in public areas, such as the comment sections of our Solve Media blog ("Public Social Features"), becomes public and anyone may take and use that information. Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any personally identifiable information that you expect to keep private. Please consult the applicable guidelines, if any, for use of our Public Social Features for more information. Solve Media cannot control who views information that you post in public areas of the Sites and is not responsible for how third parties may use or disclose information that you post in public areas of the Sites.

**_Governing Law_**

This Website is published in the United States. We attempt to protect the personally identifiable information of all users of our Website and we attempt to comply with local data protection and consumer rights laws to the extent they may apply to Solve Media's services, but our Website is targeted to United States citizens and our policies are directed at compliance with those laws. If you are uncertain whether this Privacy Policy conflicts with the applicable local privacy laws where you are located, you should not submit your personally identifiable information to Solve Media.

**_Notice to Non-US Users_**

If you are located outside the United States of America, you should be aware that your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the United States of America, the laws of which may be deemed by the your country to have inadequate data protection. If you are located in a country outside the United States of America and voluntarily submit personally identifiable information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this privacy policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States of America.

**_Children's Information_**

The Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age and Solve Media does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

**_Changes to this Policy_**

We may change the terms of our Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. Your continued use of our Website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. If we intend to apply the modifications or amendments to this Privacy Policy retroactively or to personally identifiable information already in our possession, we will provide you with notice of the modifications or amendments and seek your consent for such use.

**_How to Contact Us_**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Solve Media via e-mail at privacy@solvemedia.com with "PRIVACY POLICY" in the subject line or by mailing us at the following address:

Solve Media, Inc.  
200 S. Broad Street  
Suite 915  
Philadelphia PA, 19102

We will investigate your question, respond to your inquiry, and attempt to resolve any concerns regarding your privacy question.
